A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Leadership Development Program (LDP), Accession 2017:027 FA1298
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Southeast Region LDP Fellow files, 1960-1979; 4; 19.36 Cubic Feet About 39 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 5 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - T-Z, 1963-1979; 4; 3.74 Cubic Feet About 7.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 1 LGL size Hollinger box
    - Williams, Freddie L. - Darlington, South Carolina, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1132)
      Original folder marked Freddie Williams - Project Abstract -- 1970"
    - Williams, Freddie L. - Darlington, South Carolina, 1968-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1133-1134)
    - Williams, Mildred M. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1966-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1135-1136)
    - Williams, Mildred M. - Jackson, Mississippi, 1967-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1137)
    - Williams, Minnie M. - Alberta, Alabama, 1971-1977 (Box 85, Folder 1138)
    - Williams, Minnie M. - Alberta, Alabama, 1972-1973 (Box 85, Folder 1139)
    - Wilson, Nancy - Camden, South Carolina, 1967-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1140-1141)
    - Wilson, Nancy - Camden, South Carolina, 1968-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1142)
    - Wilson, Willie, Jr. - Letohatchee, Alabama, 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 1143)
    - Wright, JoAnn - Tuskegee, Alabama, 1972-1976 (Box 86, Folder 1144-1147)
      Within the original folder, another folder marked "JoAnn Wright -- 1973-1974 Expense Reports" had been inserted to become part of the overall file.
    - Wright, JoAnn - Tuskegee, Alabama, 1973-1974 (Box 86, Folder 1148-1149)
    - Wright, Mercedes A. - Savannah, Georgia, 1971-1977 (Box 86, Folder 1150-1152)
    - Wright, Mercedes A. - Savannah, Georgia, 1971-1974 (Box 86, Folder 1153)
    - Young, Eva M. - Philadelphia, Mississippi, 1971-1974 (Box 87, Folder 1154-1155)
    - Young, Eva M. - Philadelphia, Mississippi, 1972-1974 (Box 87, Folder 1156)
    - Young, Robert E. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1968-1974; File includes a still image of LDP Fellow Robert Young (Folder 1157). (Box 87, Folder 1157-1158)
    - Young, Robert E. - Greenville, Mississippi, 1969-1972 (Box 87, Folder 1159)
    - Zimmerman, Gilbert B. - Beaufort, South Carolina, 1970-1976 (Box 87, Folder 1160-1161)
    - Zimmerman, Gilbert B. - Beaufort, South Carolina, 1970-1971 (Box 87, Folder 1162)
- Miscellaneous materials, 1971-1972; 5; .22 Cubic Feet 1 half LTR size Hollinger box
  Series contains miscellaneous financial materials for the Ford Foundation that do not appear to possess any specific relation to the Leadership Development Program records that comprise the rest of the collection.
  Access to Series is restricted.
  - Journal supports, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 1163-1164)
    Restricted - financial material.
  - Miscellaneous inter-office charges, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 1165-1167)